<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cunxin&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://opthuang.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cunxin&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://opthuang.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://opthuang.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opthuang.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>I am a PhD student at Department of Applied Mathematics, The Hong Kong Polytechnic University, supervised by Dr. Zaikun Zhang and co-supervised Prof. Xiaojun Chen.
Research interests Link to heading My research interests mainly focus on mathematical optimization and its applications, especially
derivative-free optimization, randomized methods. Education Link to heading 2022&amp;ndash;2026 (expected), PhD student in Applied Optimization and Optimal Control, Department of Applied Mathematics, The Hong Kong Polytechnic University, Hong Kong SAR, China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://opthuang.github.io/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opthuang.github.io/blog/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://opthuang.github.io/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opthuang.github.io/papers/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of my publications.
C. Huang, H. Song, J. Yang, and B. Zhou. Error analysis of finite difference scheme for american option pricing under regime-switching with jumps. J. Comput. Appl. Math., accepted for publication, 2023. Z. Gao, C. Huang, H. Song, and B. Zhou. Projection and contraction method for pricing american option under regime-switching model. Journal of Jilin University (Science Edition), 60:1090-1096, 2022. To be continued!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://opthuang.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opthuang.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of my talks, linked with the websites of the conferences and my slides.
Non-convergence of Probabilistic Direct Search. The 14th International Conference on Numerical Optimization and Numerical Linear Algebra (ICNONLA2023), Taiyuan, Shanxi, China, 2023. To be continued!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Z</title>
      <link>https://opthuang.github.io/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opthuang.github.io/team/</guid>
      <description>Team Leader: Assistant Professor Zaikun Zhang (second from the right)
Team Member:
Postdoctoral Fellow Tom M. Ragonneau (second from the left) PhD Candidate Haitian Li (first from the left) PhD Student Cunxin Huang (first from the right) Group Photo with Professor Ya-xiang Yuan (middle)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
